<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hamza</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>https://ismnoiet.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://ismnoiet.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:48:36 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:48:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A must-have list of plugins for sublime text</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sublime text, is one of the most if not the most flexible hackable code editor, available for all OS with a huge list of plugins to make it even better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll be talking about the indispensable plugins that you need to install if you want to gain a huge amount of time when using sublime text , without too much talking let’s get directly to the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Files handling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Files handling is an essential part of any project, because we find our selves creating, opening a lot of files and folders.Using the traditional way(opening a file using the openfile dialog or moving the mouse around to do the job) can cost us some time and that is when the following list comes to play :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/skuroda/Sublime-AdvancedNewFile&quot;&gt;AdvancedNewFile&lt;/a&gt; :
  This plugin is excellent for creating folders and files, it can create files even if the parent folder doesn’t exist yet, which is cool and time saver .&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rosshemsley/iOpener&quot;&gt;iOpener&lt;/a&gt; :
  With this plugin we can open files from any location in our computer.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Color highlighting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those plugins are pretty convenient when it comes to picking and choosing colors especially with CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Monnoroch/ColorHighlighter&quot;&gt;Color highlighter&lt;/a&gt; :
  As the name says, it is a color highlighter so we can write the hex or rgb code for a color and we get an instantly color changing according to the given color code.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/weslly/ColorPicker&quot;&gt;ColorPicker&lt;/a&gt; :
  This is useful when we want to pick a color and we forgot or don’t know exactly its corresponding code.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTML-CSS-JS Related&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/victorporof/Sublime-HTMLPrettify&quot;&gt;HTML-CSS-JS Prettify&lt;/a&gt; :
  A plugin for prettifying HTML-CSS-JS.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/weslly/Nettuts-Fetch&quot;&gt;Nettuts+ Fetch&lt;/a&gt; :
  This is useful if we have a defined list of plugins or libraries and we need
  to add them to our current project.
  However, with the appearance of front-end tools like bower and others, handling dependencies is not an issue anymore SO we can ignore this plugin, BUT for the sake of not leaving the code editor i think you may want to keep it around.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strings manipulation Related&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jdc0589/CaseConversion&quot;&gt;Case Convertion&lt;/a&gt; : An awesome plugin to convert strings and switch  cases from camel case to snake case to whatever case you want.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note&lt;/em&gt; :
This article was originally published on &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@hamism/a-must-have-list-of-plugins-for-sublime-text-a54e865ee26#.lqgrumnxd&quot;&gt;medium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://ismnoiet.github.io/tools/2016/02/24/A-must-have-list-of-plugins-for-sublime-text.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://ismnoiet.github.io/tools/2016/02/24/A-must-have-list-of-plugins-for-sublime-text.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>tools</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
